ulsterbank.ie 2007-02-02

# Ulster Bank: Privacy Policy

## Online Privacy Policy 

This document sets out the Ulster Bank Group Privacy Policy for this site. If you have any objections to this policy, you should not access or use this site.   
Ulster Bank Group (ULSTER BANK or we) respects your right to privacy in relation to your interactions with this website. Any information which is provided by you will be treated in accordance with the terms of the Data Protection (Amendment) Act 2003 with regard to the processing of personal data. 

## Individual Rights 

Outlined below is our policy on key privacy issues as they relate to this site. In every case, we will let you know what we intend doing with that information before collecting it, so that you can decide whether or not to furnish that information to us. If at any time after giving us this information you decide that you no longer wish us to hold or use this information, or in the case that the information becomes out of date, you are free to notify us, and we will remove or rectify the information within a reasonable time. Please note that this policy statement applies only to this Web site and is not intended to reflect the policy of any outside sites linking to or from ulsterbank.com as well as ulsterbank.ie. If, at any time, you wish to contact us or have a question, you can reach us at the above website. 

## Disclosures 

ULSTER BANK, its servants and/or agents may need to verify and/or exchange certain information provided by you from time to time with financial institutions and/or other appropriate bodies. This may be because of the restrictions applicable to the use of certain facilities and/or services offered by way of this site, or to the extent otherwise necessary in connection with your use of facilities and/or services offered by way of this site. Therefore, you agree that ULSTER BANK and/or any employee, representative or agent of ULSTER BANK shall have the right to verify and/or exchange such information as provided by you and you hereby authorise any or all of such entities to contact you and/or financial institutions and/or other appropriate bodies as maybe necessary in order to verify and/or exchange the information which you have provided. 

You acknowledge and agree that in certain circumstances we may be obliged to disclose personal information relating to you to third parties, for example, in order to conform to any requirements of law or to comply with any legal process, as well as to protect and defend the rights of property of ULSTER BANK, our licensors and/or our other customers. 

## Cookies 

Cookies are small files of data that many Websites automatically store on a visitor's computer while the visitor is on that particular site, typically to help better service its visitors. 

ULSTER BANK uses cookies to provide a more personalised experience. The cookie stores information on the region you have selected, Northern Ireland, Republic of Ireland or Isle of Man, and whether you have selected personal or business information. This information is collected as you enter the ULSTER BANK web site and used to provide you with the most relevant information in the 'Select a link' facility. 

You can choose whether to allow the use of cookies on your PC. Should you choose to disable cookies on your PC you will notice no difference on the general use of the ULSTER BANK web site. 

The procedure for disabling cookies depends on the web browser that you have chosen to use. We have supplied links to the Microsoft and Netscape web sites to provide you with the procedures to follow to view and disable cookies on your PC. 

If you use Internet Explorer, [ www.microsoft.com/info/cookies.htm](http://www.microsoft.com/info/cookies.htm "Microsoft's website. Opens in a new window")

If you use Netscape, [ www.netscape.com/legal_notices/cookies.html](http://www.netscape.com/legal_notices/cookies.html "Netscape's website. Opens in a new window")

You should be aware that ULSTER BANK is unable to control the use of cookies or the resulting information by other third parties. 

## Web Trafficking Data 

As is standard with almost all Websites, this site passively collects limited logging information that we use to analyse Web traffic on our site and improve site quality. This lets us know, for example, when we may want to consider providing additional information on a given topic that seems to be popular with visitors. We use this information only for aggregate reporting, and do not use it to analyse or identify the use of our site by any specific visitor. 

## Disclaimers 

You should also be aware that where you link to another website from the ULSTER BANK website, that ULSTER BANK has no control over that website. Accordingly, ULSTER BANK cannot guarantee that the controller of that website will respect your privacy in the same manner as ULSTER BANK.   
ULSTER BANK, its directors, employees, servants and agents, affiliates or other representatives and their respective parent and subsidiary companies, shall not be liable in respect of any claims, emergencies, demands, causes of action, damages, losses, expenses, including without limitation, reasonable attorney fees and costs of in accordance with this privacy policy and your consents. 

ULSTER BANK reserves the right in its sole discretion to amend this privacy statement at any time, and you should regularly check this privacy statement for any amendments
